{"subjectID":2,"researchID":"SonificationResearch","dateTime":"2020-12-23T11:40:29.9053261+01:00","sysSpec":{"CPU":"Intel(R) Core(TM) i7-9700K CPU @ 3.60GHz","GPU":"NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 Ti","Ram":"16303Mb","OS":"Windows 10  (10.0.0) 64bit"},"answers":[{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 1 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":13.1288528,"questionAnswerTime":13.1288519},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 2 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":14.6045179,"questionAnswerTime":14.604517},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 3 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":15.7052908,"questionAnswerTime":15.70529},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 4 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":16.8709,"questionAnswerTime":16.8708973},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 5 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":18.070343,"questionAnswerTime":18.070343},{"question":"What is the mimimal noticable diffrence for this participant?","answer":"9.895554","questionAskTime":26.9392757,"questionAnswerTime":26.9392757},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"10.17329","questionAskTime":28.8561745,"questionAnswerTime":29.6243019},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"6.021644","questionAskTime":29.6260223,"questionAnswerTime":31.2137},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"1.571928","questionAskTime":31.2154236,"questionAnswerTime":31.7739544},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"11.50702","questionAskTime":31.775671,"questionAnswerTime":32.33286},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"8.653599","questionAskTime":32.334568,"questionAnswerTime":32.900383},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"11.92735","questionAskTime":32.90213,"questionAnswerTime":33.3855476},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"5.404229","questionAskTime":33.3872948,"questionAnswerTime":33.85481},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"9.067741","questionAskTime":38.6069565,"questionAnswerTime":39.718483},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"11.62118","questionAskTime":39.72021,"questionAnswerTime":40.25607},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"1.430302","questionAskTime":40.2577858,"questionAnswerTime":40.7688866},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"4.957643","questionAskTime":40.7706451,"questionAnswerTime":41.2715263},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"12.62397","questionAskTime":41.2732468,"questionAnswerTime":41.87228},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"4.969958","questionAskTime":41.8740425,"questionAnswerTime":43.5086479},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"9.029399","questionAskTime":43.51037,"questionAnswerTime":44.19282},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"5.198575","questionAskTime":48.7926331,"questionAnswerTime":49.1259079},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"1.662876","questionAskTime":49.1277847,"questionAnswerTime":49.3413658},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"8.914678","questionAskTime":49.34308,"questionAnswerTime":49.54503},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"12.65123","questionAskTime":49.5467873,"questionAnswerTime":49.71495},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"4.870531","questionAskTime":49.7166672,"questionAnswerTime":49.9055862},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"11.62287","questionAskTime":49.9073029,"questionAnswerTime":50.0977478},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"9.142941","questionAskTime":50.099556,"questionAnswerTime":50.2962761},{"question":"What is the error in condition 4?","answer":"23.5329","questionAskTime":59.6912842,"questionAnswerTime":61.63797},{"question":"What is the error in condition 4?","answer":"24.94461","questionAskTime":61.63969,"questionAnswerTime":62.36688},{"question":"What is the error in condition 4?","answer":"16.40516","questionAskTime":62.36865,"questionAnswerTime":62.9495239},{"question":"What is the error in condition 4?","answer":"15.10881","questionAskTime":62.95124,"questionAnswerTime":63.4936562},{"question":"What is the error in condition 4?","answer":"17.31392","questionAskTime":63.49542,"questionAnswerTime":64.27528},{"question":"What is the error in condition 4?","answer":"21.06387","questionAskTime":64.27701,"questionAnswerTime":64.79282},{"question":"What is the error in condition 4?","answer":"23.92396","questionAskTime":64.79457,"questionAnswerTime":65.4180145},{"question":"What is the error in condition 4?","answer":"24.95692","questionAskTime":65.41983,"questionAnswerTime":65.9180756},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":2.02899885,"questionAnswerTime":10.1563253},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":10.1570644,"questionAnswerTime":11.5722752},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":20.0730762,"questionAnswerTime":23.42115},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.4391289,"questionAnswerTime":26.9273548},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":26.9635983,"questionAnswerTime":28.8540726},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":33.85507,"questionAnswerTime":35.5460548},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":35.5597267,"questionAnswerTime":38.6049461},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 2?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":44.19307,"questionAnswerTime":45.6239624},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 3 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":45.63953,"questionAnswerTime":48.790657},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 3?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":50.29662,"questionAnswerTime":57.73319},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 4 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":57.89998,"questionAnswerTime":59.68928}]}